# Sangryul Jeon

Postdoctoral Scholar · UC Berkeley · International Computer Science Institute · srjeon@berkeley.edu · sr-jeon.github.io

#### **Interests**

The driver of my research is to develop robust *computer vision systems that can understand an object or scene* of interest even under strong geometry and appearance variations. In order to keep them practical and useful in the real-world, I'm also interested in *learning them without the need of supervision* through the techniques of self-supervising, metric learning, and domain adaptation.

## **Experience**

## UC Berkeley - Postdoctoral Scholar

Mar. 2022 - Present

- $\cdot \ \, \text{Electrical Engineering and Computer Sciences Department}$
- · Supervised by Prof. Stella X. Yu

#### Adobe - Research Intern

May. 2021 - Aug. 2021

- · Creative Intelligence Lab (San jose)
- · Worked with Zhifei Zhang, Zhe Lin, Zhihong Ding, Scott Cohen

#### Yonsei University - Research Assistant

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022

- · School of Electrical and Electronic Engineering
- · Supervised by Prof. Kwanghoon Sohn

#### **Education**

#### Philosophy of Doctorate - Yonsei University

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022

· School of Electrical and Electronic Engineering

#### Barchelor of Science - Yonsei University

Mar. 2009 - Feb. 2016

· School of Electrical and Electronic Engineering

#### **Publications**

#### **COAT: Correspondence-driven Object Appearance Transfer - Accepted**

Nov. 2022

- · Sangryul Jeon, Zhifei Zhang, Zhe Lin, Scott Cohen, Zhihong Ding, Kwanghoon Sohn
- · British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC)

## Neural Matching Fields: Implicit Representation of Matching Cost for Semantic Correspondence - Accepted

Dec. 2022

- · Sunghwan Hong, Jisu Nam, Seokju Cho, Susung Hong, **Sangryul Jeon**, Dongbo Min, Seungryong Kim
- · Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS)

## Unsupervised Scene Sketch to Photo Synthesis - Accepted

Oct. 2022

- · Jiayun Wang, **Sangryul Jeon**, Stella X. Yu, Xi Zhang, Himanshu Arora, and Yu Lou
- · European Conference on Computer Vision Workshops (ECCVW)
- · AIM: Advances in Image Manipulation workshop and challenges

#### Pyramidal Semantic Correspondence Networks - Accepted

Oct. 2021

- · Sangryul Jeon, Seungryong Kim, Dongbo Min, and Kwanghoon Sohn
- · IEEE Trans. On Pattern Analysis and Machine Intelligence (TPAMI)

CATs: Cost Aggregation Transformers for Visual Correspondence	Sep. 202
[Seokju Cho, Sunghwan Hong]*, <b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Yunsung Lee, Kwanghoon Sohn, Seungryong Kim Neural Information Processing Systems ( <b>NeurIPS</b> )	
Mining Better Samples for Contrastive Learning of Temporal Correspondence	Jun. 202
<b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Dongbo Min, Seungryong Kim, and Kwanghoon Sohn IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition ( <b>CVPR</b> )	
Guided Semantic Flow	Aug. 2020
<b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Dongbo Min, Seungryong Kim, and Kwanghoon Sohn European Conference on Computer Vision ( <b>ECCV</b> )	
Joint Learning of Semantic Alignment and Object Landmark Detection	Oct. 2019
<b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Dongbo Min, Seungryong Kim, and Kwanghoon Sohn IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision ( <b>ICCV</b> )	
Video Summarization by Learning Relationships between Action and Scene	Oct. 2019
Jungin Park, Jiyoung Lee, <b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , and Kwanghoon Sohn IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision Workshops ( <b>ICCVW</b> )  The 2nd Workshop and Challenge on Comprehensive Video Understanding in the Wild (CoVieW'20)	019)
Graph Regularization Network with Semantic Affinity for Weakly-supervised Temporal Action Localization	Sep. 2019
Jungin Park, Jiyoung Lee, <b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Seungryong Kim, and Kwanghoon Sohn IEEE International Conference on Image Processing ( <b>ICIP</b> )	
Semantic Attribute Matching Networks	Jun. 2019
Seungryong Kim, Dongbo Min, Somi Jeong, Sunok Kim, <b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , and Kwanghoon Sohn IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition ( <b>CVPR</b> )	
Recurrent Transformer networks for Semantic Correspondence - Spotlight	Dec. 2018
Seungryong Kim, Stephen Lin, <b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Dongbo Min, and Kwanghoon Sohn Neural Information Processing Systems ( <b>NeurIPS</b> )	
Learning to Detect, Associate, and Recognize Human Actions and Surrounding Scenes in Untrimmed Videos	Oct. 2018
Jungin Park, <b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Seungryong Kim, Jiyoung Lee, Sunok Kim, and Kwanghoon Sohn ACM International Conference on Multimedia Workshops ( <b>ACMMMW</b> )	
The 1st Workshop and Challenge on Comprehensive Video Understanding in the Wild	
PARN: Pyramidal Affine Regression Networks for Dense Semantic Correspondence	Sep. 2018
<b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Seungryong Kim, Dongbo Min, and Kwanghoon Sohn European Conference on Computer Vision ( <b>ECCV</b> )	
Convolutional Feature Pyramid Fusion via Attention Network	Sep. 201
<b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Seungryong Kim, and Kwanghoon Sohn IEEE International Conference on Image Processing ( <b>ICIP</b> )	
FCSS: Fully Convolutional Self-Similarity for Dense Semantic Correspondence	Jul. 201
Seungryong Kim, Dongbo Min, Bumsub Ham, <b>Sangryul Jeon</b> , Steve Lin, and Kwanghoon Sohn IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition ( <b>CVPR</b> )	

## **Projects**

Flojects	
To create AI systems that act appropriately and effectively in novel situations that occur in open worlds	Mar. 2020 - Feb. 2022
· Funded by Institute of Information & Communication Technology (IITP)	
Fundamental study of vision algorithms for comprehensive and thorough understanding of videos	Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2020
Funded by Ministry of Science, ICT and Future planning	
Development of the high-precision AR & VR contents based on smart-car sensors	Apr. 2016 - Dec.2021
· Funded by Institute of Information & Communication Technology (IITP)	
Invited Talks	
Pyramidal Affine Regression Networks for Dense Semantic Correspondence	
NAVER	Feb. 2019
·Korean Conference on Computer Vision (KCCV) 2019	Jul. 2019
Joint Learning of Semantic Alignment and Object Landmark Detection	
NAVER	Oct. 2019
·Samsung Al Forum	Nov. 2019
·Korean Conference on Computer Vision (KCCV) 2020	Aug. 2020
Understanding Object Semantics Driven by Correspondences	
·University of British Columbia hosted by Prof. Kwang Moo Yi	May. 2021
Activities	
Reviewer	
·IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)	2020-2022
·IEEE/CVF International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV)	2021
·European Conference on Computer Vision ( <b>ECCV</b> )	2022
Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS)	2020-2022
International Conference on Learning Representations (ICLR)	2021-2023
International Conference on Machine Learning (ICML)	2021-2022
·Asian Conference on Computer Vision ( <b>ACCV</b> )	2020-2022 2021-2022
·IEEE Winter Conference on Applications of Computer Vision ( <b>WACV</b> ) ·Pattern Recognition	2021-2022

## **References**

## **Kwanghoon Sohn** - Full professor

- · School of Electrical and Electronic Engineering
- · Yonsei University, Seoul, Korea

·Neurocomputing

- · Relationship: MS & Ph.D supervisor
- · E-mail: khsohn@yonsei.ac.kr